All right, here's a big one. Finish
the SynchAdapter, making it fetch the weather
and store it in the database. Alter
the updateWeather function within the ForecastFragment to
start a sync with the SyncAdapter. Some things here. Pull the code from on
handle intent into our SyncAdapter. On handle
intent is inside of our Sunshine service.
The good news is that abstract threaded
sync adapter provides a background thread to
run the server fetch on, just like
intent service does. Also, just fetch the location
query from our utility class. Eventually, we
want to run syncs like this without any
involvement of the user. Finally, make the
sync adaptor run when we call Update Weather.